<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Coastal Dash & Bash]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Coastal Dash & Bash]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/charlestondashnbash/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 16:22:09 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/charlestondashnbash/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 16:22:07 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why We Race]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Why We Race</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/1e7e7900-82ca-477e-9b64-ed4ca1322844.jpg">,<h1>Coastal Dash &amp; Bash</h1>,<p>We are all about a little bit of exercise and a whole lot of fun! We aren't about racing or being an obstacle warrior. We are about having a good time and meeting friendly people!</p>,<p>We are also really interested in contributing to non-profits in any way we can! Wounded Nature is the non-profit we are partnering with because we believe in what they do!</p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/b33b78e1-c026-4ed8-849f-bd00227162dd.png">,<p><strong>Wounded Nature</strong> – They assemble volunteer boaters, veterans and volunteers to remove debris from hard to reach coastal areas designated by Fish and Wildlife Service and Department of Natural Resources as critical wildlife areas. Their goal is to increase the amount of domestic fish, shrimp and shellfish stocks.</p>,<p>If you want to contribute to a good cause, you can <a href="http://dashandbash.com/RaceLocations.aspx">sign up</a> for the race or donate directly to Wounded Nature by clicking <a href="http://dashandbash.com/DonateWN.aspx">HERE</a></p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/charlestondashnbash/pardons/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">abb0647c-c66a-4ba1-a8e4-25b7b39ba282</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 21:30:53 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Event Information]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1><strong>Event Information</strong></h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/9ab9eadd-b68d-4c0e-8332-4ac2970d9e63.jpg">,<h1><strong>The Race</strong></h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/a5e80db5-dc08-426d-b01f-22f8f82807aa.jpg">,<p>We try to make this event as inclusive as possible by offering three ways to participate in the DASH! (<em><strong>RUN/JOG/WALK</strong>)</em></p>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/be52d506-79c9-41ca-a329-4140bb50190b.jpg" title="Fuel for Endurance">,<h1><strong>3 CHUG -N- GO STOPS - </strong>Offering wine, beer and H2o</h1>,<h1><strong>7-Fun Obstacles</strong></h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/1634cc21-cd7a-4164-9f78-820865d875e4.jpg">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/a62cb0f0-4654-4238-b33c-956a0edadff2.jpg">,<ul><li>Driftwood Challenge - angled balance beams</li><li>Surf’s up - “floating” surfboard from bridges to walk across</li><li>Cargo Net Crawl</li><li>Beached Whale - Large sand bag drag</li><li>Sand Bag Toss - stacking smaller sandbags to a line OR how far can you toss sandbags</li><li>Piling Hop - Different levels of “pilings” to walk across</li><li>Shark Attack - Be the lifeguard and carry a weighted dummy to “safety”</li><li>Tire Hopscotch/Climb - Tire obstacle with tires to hop through and climb over/under</li><li>All Tied Up - Web of bungee bands or plastic rings tied around legs to Hop to end of obstacle</li><li>Loose Dinghy - Pull a “small boat” around obstacles to the end of stretch</li><li>Save the Swimmers - Life Ring toss</li><li>Avoid the Bottles - hanging/swinging bags with printed bottle wraps on bags</li></ul>,<p>NO PAIN JUST FUN!</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/charlestondashnbash/esprit-de-corps/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">34b594bf-61d3-42c4-93d6-aae73f039c8f</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 14:24:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Refreshments]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Refreshments</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/a614aa97-e7ad-4e46-8f4a-16314b0e4fd0.jpg">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/0cd7b3a6-ece3-427d-990d-ea27bd02eec4.png">,<h1>Info here</h1>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/charlestondashnbash/discipline-and-training/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">68133cd8-edad-48cd-a151-6e1708772b4c</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 15:52:22 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Let the GOOD TIMES Roll]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/568677f1-7487-4741-9151-4b169969903d.jpg">,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/48bc22ef-671b-4ba2-8c01-e340b67390fd.jpg">,<h1>Let the GOOD TIMES Roll</h1>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/charlestondashnbash/let-the-good-times-roll/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a69b1219-40e7-48c3-8717-3ddfb45f1cf9</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 10:56:44 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[WHAT TO BRING?]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/ebd7569d-28e2-4d4e-a4ac-e0e5681ea04f.jpg">,<h1><strong>WHAT TO BRING?</strong></h1>,<ul><li><strong>Your Signed Waiver</strong> Download Waiver</li><li><strong>Running Gear</strong> (Costumes Encouraged!)</li><li><strong>Photo ID</strong></li></ul>,<p><strong>Optional</strong></p>,<ul><li>Blanket or Lawn Chairs for the Festival and Fun Zone (You will want to stay for this one!)</li><li><strong>Cash</strong></li><li>For parking ($10), food trucks, Dash and Bash gear and more visits to the Chug N Go stops</li><li>Sunscreen</li><li>A Car Full of Friends with a Designated Driver!</li></ul>,<p>MORE FAQs</p>,<ul><li><em><strong>Q: Can I just attend the festival?</strong></em></li><li>A: Absolutely! We have gathered some of the best food trucks and adult beverage providers together and music that will get you moving!!</li><li><em><strong>Q: Do you need volunteers?</strong></em></li><li>A: Yes, we do and would love to have you join us! We couldn’t do it without our fabulous volunteers that help get everyone amped at registration, help set-up and break-down, and continuously add to the awesome VIBE by cheering everyone on! Plus, you get free entry to the festival, a water bottle, and a bring a friend discount! Click here to volunteer and help out!</li><li><em><strong>Q: What are the minimum and maximum ages?</strong></em></li><li>A: 21 is the minimum age to attend the event either as a participant, and there is no minimum age for the festival. Families should be aware that there is a festival atmosphere among adults and Dash and Bash is not responsible for language, and PDA of our guests. There’s no maximum age.</li><li><em><strong>Q: Is the race stroller friendly?</strong></em></li><li>A: Nope, sorry.</li><li><em><strong>Q: Do designated driver-runners get a non-alcoholic drink?</strong></em></li><li>A: YES! Free water and sodas come with your designated driver wristband! Thank you for helping everyone drink responsibly! OR (Each runner that you drive earns you a non-alcoholic drink with Dash and Bash tokens – claim these upon entry for spectators or after the race for participants!)</li><li><em><strong>Q: Do you provide refunds or credits?</strong></em></li><li>A: No, but we do offer the ability to transfer your registration to someone else. Simply use this link to request the transfer.</li><li><em><strong>Q: Is this race timed and are their awards?</strong></em></li><li>A: The race is not timed, but we do offer awards throughout the event for creative purposes while at the festival! Perhaps there might be a surprise award at an obstacle challenge along the way as well!</li><li><em><strong>Q: What happens if it rains?</strong></em></li><li>A: The Dash and Bash will go on…unless we are channeling NOAH or if there is a serious threat to our guests due to lightening or winds at tropical storm or higher gusts! To read more about our weather policy click here.</li><li><em><strong>Q: What about spectators and kids?</strong></em></li><li>A: Spectators? At Dash and Bash nobody is a spectator! We welcome family and friends to enjoy the fun-filled festival with you! There will be a fun zone for kiddos and an even MORE FUN ZONE for adults!</li><li><em><strong>Q: What do I get with my registration?</strong></em></li><li>A: You get:<ul><li>Finishers Medal</li><li>Festival and Vendor Village</li><li>Dash and Bash Water Bottle (from Coastal Challenge)</li><li>Race Bib</li><li>Water Stations</li><li>Photographers Onsite</li><li>Free Photos</li><li>Gear Check ($5 donation)</li><li>Giving to a Good Cause</li><li>Live DJ</li><li>Loads of Fun with Family and Friends</li></ul></li></ul>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/charlestondashnbash/what-to-bring/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7fcab46f-5ff0-4e35-868d-9c3f288224bb</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 20:33:23 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>